ISMAIL BENTABET

Saida, Ain-Elhdjar, DZ | +213 (794) 75-3644 | <u>ismailbentabett@gmail.com</u> <u>github.com/ismailbentabett</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/ismailbentabett</u> | <u>ismailbentabett | ismailbentabett | ismailbentabet</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Frontend Developer with six years of experience working in small and large teams eager to relocate for exciting opportunities and contribute expertise in developing interactive and user-friendly web applications and Web APIs. A self-motivated and lifelong learner familiar with modern web technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

EURL Télécom Radio Professionnel | Full Stack Engineer

Jun 2023 - Dec 2023 | Remote, France

- Enhanced <u>TRP</u>'s CMS backend and frontend features using Laravel 10, Vue 3, and Tailwind CSS
- Collaborated on integrating Laravel 10, Vue 3, Inertiajs, and Tailwind CSS, FilamentPHP, for a cohesive user interface
- Contributed to increased user engagement and positive feedback. Deployed using Docker and AWSElastic Beanstalk

Software Engineer & Co-founder| Shortcut

Oct 2022- Jun 2023 | Algeria, Algiers

- Initiated and led the development of an <u>Online</u>
 <u>Work Platform</u> using JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js
 & Nestjs & Nuxt.Js
- Guided a compact development team, ensuring project delivery within 6 months, and contributing to startup growth

Junior Software Engineer | Sig-Service

May 2022 - Oct 2022 | Algeria, Algiers

- Developed and implemented the <u>SFA-13</u> CRM & <u>Acile App</u>, connecting a Vuejs & Capacitor & ionic App seamlessly with Odoo API
- Maintained technologies: JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js, Cypress, HTML, CSS, Tailwindcss, Nuxt.Js
- Integrated modules, optimising Sales, Accounting, Lead, Human Resources, CRM, and Reporting functionalities and performed end-to-end tests.
- experience working in a self-hosted GitLab environment

Software Engineer & Co-founder| Shortcut

Jul 2020- May 2022 | Algeria, Algiers

- Initiated and led the development of an <u>Online</u>
 <u>Work Platform</u> using JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js
 & Nestjs & Nuxt.Js
- Guided a compact development team, ensuring project delivery within 6 months, and contributing to startup growth

SKILLS

Languages

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript

Technologies

Vue.Js (2 and 3), Nuxt.Js, Vuetify, Tailwind CSS, Vue Router, Pinia, Vuex, Vitest, GIT.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Jan 2018 - Jun 2022 | Algeria, Algier University of Dr Tahar MOULAY Saida

PROJECTS

Freelance Fullstack Developer, TRP (trp-france.fr)

- Enhanced TRP's CMS backend and frontend features using Laravel 10, Vue 3, and Tailwind CSS
- Collaborated on integrating Laravel 10, Vue 3, Inertiajs, and Tailwind CSS, FilamentPHP, for a cohesive UI

Developer, Screamer(github.com/Screamer)

- developed features for the screamer project, integrating Angular and .NET Core with Domain-Driven Design principles
- Enhanced user experience and functionality using Tailwind CSS for cohesive styling

Developer, Silikan (github.com/silikan)

- Implemented features for backend and frontend using Laravel 10, Vue 3, and Tailwind CSS
- Integrated Laravel 10, Vue 3, and Tailwind CSS seamlessly for a cohesive and responsive user interface

Developer, NeverNote (github.com/NeverNote)

- Developed and implemented a note-taking app using vue.js and ionic
- Integrated Firebase and Quillis for a better user experience

Developer, ISICONIC (isiconic web app)

- Developed and implemented a social media platform directed for online shoppers made with mevn stack (MongoDB, vue, node, express)
- Integrated technologies like socket.io for chat and vuetify for UI

Developer, Sweetr (github.com/Sweetr)

 Developed and implemented a Twitter clone using SolidJs and Laravel

Developer, Portfolio (ismailbentabett.com)

• Developed Portfolio Using React

Languages

English - C2, Arabic - Native, French - B2